titanbet.com 2010-12-31

# Security & Privacy

### Security

At Titan Bet, we take security issues very seriously and aim to provide our players with the highest security standards possible. It is imperative to us that you feel your personal details are 100% secure before you start placing bets with us. If you have any questions regarding security issues, please contact our support team. 

**Information Protection**  
Titan Bet has adopted the most sophisticated technology to guarantee the security and protection of your privacy. Your account information and deposits are fully protected by state-of-the-art security systems, software and services. 

**Fraud Control**  
The security measures implemented by Titan Bet ensure the validity of each transaction you make, while the latest fraud control systems are utilized to protect your credit card information. 

**Encryption**  

Titan Bet uses Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology on all web pages that contain your personal information. SSL works by encrypting all the data by using complex mathematical algorithms, to ensure we maintain the highest possible level of web security and that all your information remains secure and private at all times. 

**Confidentiality**

Any and all information received from players is held in the strictest of confidence by Titan Bet. Player information will never be forwarded to any organization for commercial or any other gain, save that required by law. 

The privacy and security of all our players is of the utmost importance to Titan Bet. When playing at Titan Bet you can be assured that we will respect and protect your privacy - so that you are free to enjoy the best online gambling available. Below is a summary of our Privacy Policy.

### Privacy Policy

 ****  
This Privacy Policy sets out the data processing practices carried out through the use of the Internet and any other electronic communications networks by Titan Bet. If you have any requests concerning your personal information or any queries with regard to these practices please contact us at support(put the 'at' sign here)titanbet.com

 **Information collected**  
We collect personal information from visitors to this web site through the use of online forms and every time you e-mail us your details. We also collect information about the transactions you undertake including details of payment cards used. The personal information that we collect may include your name, email address, home address, telephone number, debit/credit card data and date of birth and other information collected on registration or through surveys which we, or undertakings engaged by us for such purpose, shall undertake. 

We collect additional information automatically about your visit to our web site. 

**Use of personal information**  
We process your personal information for the purposes of: 

  * (a) creating and managing player accounts and records;
  * (b) administering player accounts;
  * (c) providing and personalising our services;
  * (d) dealing with your enquiries and requests;
  * (e) notifying you about updates to our software and/or services;
  * (f) ensuring we are able to fulfil our regulatory responsibilities by verifying the accuracy of any information you give us;
  * (g) our general regulatory compliance, crime prevention and prosecution of offenders including, where appropriate, dealing with requests for information by sports authorities or other authorised entities for the sharing of information;
  * (h) carrying out market research campaigns;
  * (i) providing you with information about and support for products and services;
  * (j) marketing our services or products or those of other entities within our group of companies; and
  * (k) supporting any of the intended purposes specifically stated at the time at which you provided the personal information.

These are the “ **Purposes** ” for which we may collect personal data. 

**Disclosure of personal information**  
We may, for the Purposes, disclose your personal information to any of the following recipients (“ **Recipients** ”): 

  * (i) any companies within our group and to their employees who have a need to know such information;
  * (ii) any third parties which provide services to us in order to allow or enable us to provide you with gambling services, including by way of example payment processors and data verifiers; 
  * (iii) any third parties who provide services to us in relation to the operation of Titan Bet;
  * (iv) any auditors, contractors or other advisers auditing any of our business processes or who have the need to access such information for the purpose of advising us;
  * (v) any regulatory body, sports body or authorised entity who may have any reasonable requirement to access such personal information; and
  * (vi) any potential purchasers of the Titan Bet business or any investors in it or in any company within our group. 

We may also use and disclose information in aggregate (so that no individuals are identified) for marketing and strategic development purposes. 

**Other web sites**  
Our web site may contain links to other web sites which are outside our control and are not covered by this Privacy Policy. If you access other sites using the links provided, the operators of these sites may collect information from you which will be used by them in accordance with their privacy policy, which may differ from ours. 

**Access right**  
You have a right to access the personal data held about you. To obtain a copy of the personal information we hold about you, please contact us at support(put the 'at' sign here)titanbet.com. 

**Internet-based transfers**  
Given that the Internet is a global environment, using the Internet to collect and process personal data necessarily involves the transmission of data on an international basis. Therefore, by browsing this web site and communicating electronically with us, you acknowledge and agree to our processing of personal data in this way and acknowledge the transfer of the personal data we collect to authorised recipients outside the European Economic Area. 

**Use of cookies generally**  
A cookie is a small piece of information sent by a web server to a web browser, which enables the server to collect information from the browser. Find out more about the use of cookies on [http://www.cookiecentral.com](http://www.cookiecentral.com/). 

We use cookies to identify you when you visit this web site and to keep track of your browsing patterns and build up a demographic profile. 

Most browsers allow you to turn off cookies. If you want to know how to do this please look at the help menu on your browser. However, switching off cookies will restrict your ability to make full use of the functionality available on our web site. 

**Protection of Minors**  
The services provided by the Company are not intended for or directed to minors or persons under the age of legal consent. Any person who provides us with personal information represents to us that they are 18 years of age or over the age of legal consent in their jurisdiction. We reserve the right to access and verify any personal information submitted by or collected from you. If we become aware that a minor has attempted to or has submitted personal information, we may not accept this information and may take steps to remove such information from our records. This is without prejudice to any other terms and conditions you accept when using our web site 

**Retention**  
Your personal information will not be stored for any longer period than is necessary for the purposes for which it was collected. 

**Updating this privacy policy**  
This Privacy Policy is subject to change, so please check it regularly. We reserve the right to amend or modify this Privacy Policy at any time and in response to changes in applicable data protection and privacy legislation. In the event the Purposes change, we will notify you as soon as possible and, where required, seek your consent where such notification relates to a new additional purpose for processing. 

If you have any enquiry about this Privacy Policy please write to support(put the 'at' sign here)titanbet.com. 

We are guided by a strict mail policy as detailed below: 

### Mail policy

We do not tolerate spam.   
We received your consent for communication via email.   
We send you promotional emails and updates until such time as you inform us that you no longer wish to receive them. 

You may notify us of your wish to unsubscribe at any time by: 

  * Clicking on the unsubscribe link shown in all Titan Bet emails and following the instructions.
  * Contacting us through online chat
  * Emailing us at support(put the 'at' sign here)titanbet.com

Upon receiving your notice, we will immediately stop sending you such e-mails and updates.

If you continue to receive promotional e-mails and updates or any other unsolicited communication from us after you have asked to unsubscribe, please report this to us at abuse(put the 'at' sign here)titanbet.com.
